

Ákos Dabasi **Embedded Software Developer**

Contact



+36203145941



dabasi.akos@gmail.com

Languages

Hungarian - native

English - C2

Spanish - B1/B2

German - B1/B2

French - B1/B2

About Me

Thanks to my education in Mechatronics, I have a strong understanding of electrical, mechanical and software engineering. I also have a diverse professional experience, which I believe demonstrates well my ability and willingness to continue learning and mastering new skills.

Work Experience

Embedded Software Developer, AVL Hungary Kft.

January 2023 - September 2024

I developed AUTOSAR automotive software on embedded platforms with a main focus on the communication stack and CDD components.

Technical Application Specialist, Epicor Hungary Kft.

October 2022 - January 2023

I helped clients to solve technical problems and maintained their databases.

English Teacher, Salesianos Puertollano

September 2021 - July 2022

C++ Software Developer, Cadline Kft.

March 2020 - September 2021

I developed features on a 3D CAD software in C/C++.

Application Engineer, National Instruments Hungary Kft.

July 2019 - January 2020

I provided measurement & automation solutions to customers using NI hardware and software.

Education

Mechatronics Engineering, Technical University of Budapest

September 2016 - June 2021

- Specialisation: Industrial Engineering
- Final Thesis: Building a Smart Home model for demonstration purposes.
 - Technologies involved: React, Node.is, MQTT, C/C++, STM32F103RBT6, ESP8268,

Mechatronics, Karlsruher Institut für Technologie

September 2018 - February 2019

Mechatronik und Informationstechnik

<u>Skills</u>

- C, C++
- AUTOSAR Communication Modules, MISRA C
- Embedded Systems (ESP8268, Arduino, STM32)
 - digital electronics
 - communication protocols (SPI, UART, I2C, CAN, MQTT)
- Web Development fundamentals(HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Express, MongoDB)
- Linux fundamentals
- SQL
- Git, GitHub